[
 {
 "question": "One",
 "answer": "Eins"
 },
 {
 "question": "Two",
 "answer": "Zwei"
 },
 {
 "question": "Three",
 "answer": "Drei"
 },
 {
 "question": "Four",
 "answer": "Vier"
 },
 {
 "question": "Five",
 "answer": "Fünf"
 },
 {
 "question": "Six",
 "answer": "Sechs"
 },
 {
 "question": "Seven",
 "answer": "Sieben"
 },
 {
 "question": "Eight",
 "answer": "Acht"
 },
 {
 "question": "Nine",
 "answer": "Neun"
 },
 {
 "question": "Ten",
 "answer": "Zehn"
 },
 {
 "question": "Eleven",
 "answer": "Elf"
 },
 {
 "question": "Tweleve",
 "answer": "Zwölf"
 },
 {
 "question": "Thirteen",
 "answer": "Dreizehn"
 },
 {
 "question": "Fourteen",
 "answer": "Vierzehn"
 },
 {
 "question": "Fifteen",
 "answer": "Fünfzehn"
 },
 {
 "question": "Sixteen",
 "answer": "Sechzehn"
 },
 {
 "question": "Seventeen",
 "answer": "Siebzehn"
 },
 {
 "question": "Eighteen",
 "answer": "Achtzehn"
 },
 {
 "question": "Nineteen",
 "answer": "Neunzehn"
 },
 {
 "question": "Twenty",
 "answer": "Zwanzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Twenty one",
 "answer": "Einundzwanzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Twenty two",
 "answer": "Zweiundzwanzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Twenty three",
 "answer": "Dreiundzwanzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Twenty four",
 "answer": "Vierundzwanzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Twenty five",
 "answer": "Fünfundzwanzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Twenty six",
 "answer": "Sechsundzwanzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Twenty seven",
 "answer": "Siebundzwanzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Twenty eight",
 "answer": "Achtundzwanzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Twenty nine",
 "answer": "Neunundzwanzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Thirty",
 "answer": "Dreißig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Thirty one",
 "answer": "Einunddreißig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Thirty two",
 "answer": "Zweiunddreißig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Thirty three",
 "answer": "Dreiunddreißig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Thirty four",
 "answer": "Vierunddreißig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Thirty five",
 "answer": "Fünfunddreißig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Thirty six",
 "answer": "Sechsunddreißig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Thirty seven",
 "answer": "Siebunddreißig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Thirty eight",
 "answer": "Achtunddreißig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Thirty nine",
 "answer": "Neununddreißig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Forty",
 "answer": "Vierzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Forty one",
 "answer": "Einundvierzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Forty two",
 "answer": "Zweiundvierzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Forty three",
 "answer": "Dreiundvierzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Forty four",
 "answer": "Vierundvierzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Forty five",
 "answer": "Fünfundvierzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Forty six",
 "answer": "Sechsundvierzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Forty seven",
 "answer": "Siebundvierzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Forty eight",
 "answer": "Achtundvierzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Forty nine",
 "answer": "Neunundvierzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Fifty",
 "answer": "Fünfzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Fifty one",
 "answer": "Einundfünfzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Fifty two",
 "answer": "Zweiundfünfzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Fifty three",
 "answer": "Dreiundfünfzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Fifty four",
 "answer": "Vierundfünfzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Fifty five",
 "answer": "Fünfundfünfzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Fifty six",
 "answer": "Sechsundfünfzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Fifty seven",
 "answer": "Siebundfünfzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Fifty eight",
 "answer": "Achtundfünfzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Fifty nine",
 "answer": "Neunundfünfzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Sixty",
 "answer": "Sechzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Sixty one",
 "answer": "Einundsechzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Sixty two",
 "answer": "Zweiundsechzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Sixty three",
 "answer": "Dreiundsechzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Sixty four",
 "answer": "Vierundsechzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Sixty five",
 "answer": "Fünfundsechzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Sixty six",
 "answer": "Sechsundsechzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Sixty seven",
 "answer": "Siebundsechzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Sixty eight",
 "answer": "Achtundsechzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Sixty nine",
 "answer": "Neunundsechzig"
 },
{
 "question": "Seventy",
 "answer": "Siebzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Seventy one",
 "answer": "Einundsiebzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Seventy two",
 "answer": "Zweiundsiebzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Seventy three",
 "answer": "Dreiundsiebzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Seventy four",
 "answer": "Vierundsiebzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Seventy five",
 "answer": "Fünfundsiebzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Seventy six",
 "answer": "Sechsundsiebzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Seventy seven",
 "answer": "Siebundsiebzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Seventy eight",
 "answer": "Achtundsiebzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Seventy nine",
 "answer": "Neunundsiebzig"
 },
{
 "question": "Eighty",
 "answer": "Achtzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Eighty one",
 "answer": "Einundachtzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Eighty two",
 "answer": "Zweiundachtzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Eighty three",
 "answer": "Dreiundachtzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Eighty four",
 "answer": "Vierundachtzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Eighty five",
 "answer": "Fünfundachtzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Eighty six",
 "answer": "Sechsundachtzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Eighty seven",
 "answer": "Siebundachtzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Eighty eight",
 "answer": "Achtundachtzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Eighty nine",
 "answer": "Neunundachtzig"
 },
{
 "question": "Ninety",
 "answer": "Neunzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Ninety one",
 "answer": "Einundneunzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Ninety two",
 "answer": "Zweiundneunzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Ninety three",
 "answer": "Dreiundneunzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Ninety four",
 "answer": "Vierundneunzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Ninety five",
 "answer": "Fünfundneunzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Ninety six",
 "answer": "Sechsundneunzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Ninety seven",
 "answer": "Siebundneunzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Ninety eight",
 "answer": "Achtundneunzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "Ninety nine",
 "answer": "Neunundneunzig"
 },
{
 "question": "One hundred",
 "answer": "Einhundert"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred one",
 "answer": "Einhunderteins"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred two",
 "answer": "Einhundertzwei"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred three",
 "answer": "Einhundertdrei"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred four",
 "answer": "Einhundertvier"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred five",
 "answer": "Einhundertfünf"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred six",
 "answer": "Einhundertsechs"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred seven",
 "answer": "Einhundertsieben"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred eight",
 "answer": "Einhundertacht"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred nine",
 "answer": "Einhundertneun"
 },
{
 "question": "One hundred ten",
 "answer": "Einhundertzehn"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred eleven",
 "answer": "Einhundertelf"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred twelve",
 "answer": "Einhundertzwölf"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred thirteen",
 "answer": "Einhundertdreizehn"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred fourteen",
 "answer": "Einhundertvierzehn"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred fifteen",
 "answer": "Einhundertfünfachtzehn"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred sixteen",
 "answer": "Einhundertsechzehn"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred seventeen",
 "answer": "Einhundertsiebzehn"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred eighteen",
 "answer": "Einhundertachtzehn"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred nineteen",
 "answer": "Einhundertneunzehn"
 },
{
 "question": "One hundred twenty",
 "answer": "Einhundertzwanzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred twenty one",
 "answer": "Einhunderteinundzwanzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred twenty two",
 "answer": "Einhundertzweiundzwanzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred twenty three",
 "answer": "Einhundertdreiundzwanzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred twenty four",
 "answer": "Einhundertvierundzwanzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred twenty five",
 "answer": "Einhundertfünfundzwanzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred twenty six",
 "answer": "Einhundertsechsundzwanzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred twenty seven",
 "answer": "Einhundertsiebundzwanzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred twenty eight",
 "answer": "Einhundertachtundzwanzig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred twenty nine",
 "answer": "Einhundertneunundzwanzig"
 },
{
 "question": "One hundred thirty",
 "answer": "Einhundertdreißig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred thirty",
 "answer": "Einhunderteinunddreißig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred thirty two",
 "answer": "Einhundertzweiunddreißig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred thirty three",
 "answer": "Einhundertdreiunddreißig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred thirty four",
 "answer": "Einhundertvierunddreißig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred thirty five",
 "answer": "Einhundertfünfunddreißig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred thirty six",
 "answer": "Einhundertsechsunddreißig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred thirty seven",
 "answer": "Einhundertsiebunddreißig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred thirty eight",
 "answer": "Einhundertachtunddreißig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred thirty nine",
 "answer": "Einhundertneununddreißig"
 },
{
 "question": "One hundred forty",
 "answer": "Einhundertvierßig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred forty one",
 "answer": "Einhunderteinundvierßig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred forty two",
 "answer": "Einhundertzweiundvierßig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred forty three",
 "answer": "Einhundertdreiundvierßig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred forty four",
 "answer": "Einhundertvierundvierßigg"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred forty five",
 "answer": "Einhundertfünfundvierßig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred forty six",
 "answer": "Einhundertsechsundvierßig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred forty seven",
 "answer": "Einhundertsiebundvierßig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred forty eight",
 "answer": "Einhundertachtundvierßig"
 },
 {
 "question": "One hundred forty nine",
 "answer": "Einhundertneunundvierßig"
 },
{
 "question": "One hundred fifty",
 "answer": "Einhundertfünfzig"
 }
]
